dp-db.com 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy | www.dp-db.com

## Privacy Policy

Our website, [www.dp-db.com](http://www.dp-db.com/ "www.dp-db.com"), is committed to protecting the privacy of your visits. Below, we have described our privacy policy.

### Collection of personal information:

When you register at our website, we collect the following information:

  * E-mail address
  * Your desired username
  * The city and country of residence (optional information)

Your e-mail is kept private at all times. We do not disclose it, rent it or sell it to any third party for any reason. Your username shows up on our website whenever you post a review of a certain product. City and country of residence are noted along the review if you have given us that information.

### Browsing information:

We collect information about aggregate numbers of page views and clicks in order to analyse popularity of different pages on our website and improve the quality of the site. We do not collect any users' personal information during this process. Cookies are used on our website to improve user experience and for collecting basic metrics. You can disable cookies by changing the settings on your computer.

### Security:

We are committed to ensuring that your personal information stays private and secure. Therefore we use different measures to prevent unauthorised access to our system.

Our website has links to other sites. We don't have control over these websites in any way. If you provide any information during you visit to these sites, we are no longer responsible for the security and privacy of this information. You should look for the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Changes to privacy policy:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us through our contact form and we'll get back to you as soon as possible.

Updated: May 17, 2011
